#### **AMRUTA JADHAV**

+49 1783614793 | amruta319jadhav@gmail.com | Ingolstadt, Germany https://amrutajadhav-portfolio-dev-ed.develop.my.site.com

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Overall 10+ years of experience in the IT industry and relevant 6+ years in Salesforce development and administration. I am positive, enthusiastic, proactive and good team player having extensive knowledge in the implementing, customizing and maintaining Salesforce solutions. Worked on Service cloud, Sales cloud and Experience (Community) cloud.

#### **SKILLS**

Apex, Triggers, Lightning Components (Aura and LWC), Batch Apex, Lightning Flow, SOQL, Security Settings, Data Integrations, Data Migration using Data import wizard, data loader, Reports and Dashboards

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Sr. Platform Developer, Johnson Control

12/2022 - 07/2023

- Worked on BSNA project and I was part of Enhancement team in the HVAC Domain.
- Worked on Configurations, Integration as well as Customization like apex classes, triggers, lightning components, lightning flows.
- Involved in client communication over Team channels.

# Sr. Software Professional, Extentia Information Technology

07/2022 - 12/2022

- I was part of Research and Development team and responsible for developing Proof of Concepts (POC's) according to business requirement.
- Worked on Configurations like security settings, lightning flows, Surveys and customization like batch process in the POC.

# Engineering Lead, Persistent Systems

12/2019 - 07/2022

- I was responsible for development and worked on Case Management. Used Email to case, Web to Case features and created a community where the customers can create, update and manage their cases for Baxter International client.
- I was responsible for requirement gathering and analysis of product Kisan Credit Card (KCC) introduced by IDFC bank.

## Software Developer, Cybage Software

12/2014 - 12/2019

 Worked on Athenahealth CRM project. I was responsible for requirement gathering, analysis, development, bug-fixing, unit testing, deployment, documentation along with improving test code coverage.

# Software Developer, <u>Edreamz Technology</u>

05/2013 - 12/2014

 Developed LMS website which tracks the student data. This application has Admin, Consultant and User roles. Admin can assign the batch of students to consultant. Consultant imports the student's data from excel and keep track on it. User/Student can view their report in this system.

### CERTICATIONS

- Salesforce certified Administrator
- Salesforce certified Platform Developer I
- Salesforce certified Service Cloud Consulting
- Goethe certified German A1 level

### **EDUCATION**

Master in Computer Science at Pune University, 2012

#### LANGUAGES

• English, German (Beginner)